The kettle and the idol
Then, the third element.
Jap moe.
How about this one?
I guess everyone's image of me is that of a cool idol.
I actually love cute things.
I love cute things so much that I think I'm more of a girl than anyone else.
That's why I love those cool flowers that you show at live performances and cute flowers that you show on your instagrams and photos.
I thought it would be an important element for me to create a gap between the cool flowers I show at live performances and the cute flowers I show on my Instagram or in my photos, so I included it.
I see.
I've been watching Kojima-san for quite a while.
He's going in a cool direction.
There are many things that I thought were cool about him.
When did you start aiming for coolness?
I'm not sure when you say when I started.
There is a song called "Batgirl" that AmeFlash became a cool idol.
There's a song called Batgirl.
That's when we started to incorporate cool elements into our idols.
Since then, I've had a short cut, so I was a bit boyish.
I had a short cut, so I was a bit boyish.
I started getting a lot of comments about how cool Hana-chan was.
So I started to lose my bangs and make my hair shorter.
I also made my hair a little shorter.
I also tried to make my dancing style cooler.
I thought I'd do some research and try to become a cool girl.
That's what I started doing.
Do you think you are cool or cute in your opinion?
Which makes you happier in your current situation?
Well...
I'm probably happier when fans say I'm cool.
I'm trying to be cool.I'm trying to be cool.
Until recently, Amefurashi didn't have many female fans.
We didn't have a lot of female fans before.
But recently we've been getting a lot of female fans, and we're happy to see the women's area filled up at our shows.
I'm happy to see that the women's area is filled up at our live shows.
I'm very happy to hear that women think I'm cool, and I'm also happy to hear that men think I'm cool, too.
I also think it's a true sentiment when men say I'm cool too.
Cute is a common word, isn't it, from men to women?
I think it's very rare for a man to say "cool" to a woman, so I'm happy to hear that.
So it makes me happy to hear that.
It's true that you have many female customers.
Yes, there are a lot of them, and it makes me really happy.
I'd love to get yellow cheers from the audience.
Please come to our concerts, ladies!
I'll do my best to talk to them and take some pictures.
You're very shy, aren't you?
This program is being broadcast by
Ms. Pakta
Maya-san
Mr. Toriyama
Mr. Yoshiuki
This program was provided by Tomo-san!
It's hot, so everyone be careful!